// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I and my friends … in the library. We read some books",
    answer: "are",
    options: [
      "am",
      "is",
      "have",
      "are"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "She … not work because she has the flu.",
    answer: "does",
    options: [
      "is",
      "does",
      "do",
      "be"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Alina … song every night.",
    answer: "sings",
    options: [
      "sings",
      "sing",
      "is",
      "does"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "My father … tea every morning.",
    answer: "drinks",
    options: [
      "drink",
      "drinks",
      "drinking",
      "is"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "They … a test every week",
    answer: "have",
    options: [
      "does",
      "has",
      "are",
      "have"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Dolph: Please call me if you need.<br>Jack: No. I … need your help.",
    answer: "do not",
    options: [
      "do not",
      "does",
      "not",
      "am not"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "She is a student. She … at school.",
    answer: "studies",
    options: [
      "studying",
      "study",
      "studies",
      "does"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "We … soccer match.",
    answer: "watch",
    options: [
      "doing",
      "watching",
      "watches",
      "watch"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Gina cooks fried rice. It … amazing.",
    answer: "is",
    options: [
      "does",
      "do",
      "are",
      "is"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "My brother rides a bike to school …",
    answer: "every day",
    options: [
      "every day",
      "last day",
      "next week",
      "next time"
    ]
  },
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];